{
  "exercises": [
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: Pizza is eaten.",
      "answer": "pizza wird gegessen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The book is read.",
      "answer": "das buch wird gelesen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The car is washed.",
      "answer": "das auto wird gewaschen"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: Tea is drunk.",
      "answer": "tee wird getrunken"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: Cricket is played.",
      "answer": "cricket wird gespielt"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The cake is baked by my mother.",
      "answer": "der kuchen wird von meiner mutter gebacken"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The letter is written by Hasan.",
      "answer": "der brief wird von hasan geschrieben"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The homework is done by Ankit.",
      "answer": "die hausaufgabe wird von ankit gemacht"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The window is opened by the child.",
      "answer": "das fenster wird von dem kind geöffnet"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The ball is found by the boy.",
      "answer": "der ball wird von dem jungen gefunden"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: Pizza can be eaten.",
      "answer": "pizza kann gegessen werden"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: The window must be opened.",
      "answer": "das fenster muss geöffnet werden"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: German should be learned.",
      "answer": "deutsch soll gelernt werden"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: Cricket can be played.",
      "answer": "cricket kann gespielt werden"
    },
    {
      "question": "Translate to German: Tea must be drunk.",
      "answer": "tee muss getrunken werden"
    }
  ]
}
